

### Profile

 I'm a Full stack .NET Developer with over 3 years of experience designing, building and customizing web solutions, specifically with .NET, Angular and Microsoft Azure. I apply SOLID, CLEAN, TDD and other engineering kung fu... But always try to use KISS principle. Microsoft certified, easily adaptable and ready to tackle any problem thrown at me.

# Employment History

### Independent contractor

November 2021 — Present

Full Stack Web Developer at Adastra Studios INC, California, Remote February 2022 — Present

#### Tech stack:

- · NodeJS, .NET
- Frontend development (React, vanilla JS)
- Cloud programming (MS Azure, GCP, small cloud providers)

My job was to migrate existing codebase to Azure and GCP, as well as help write and maintain existing custom services for managing game servers (pixel streaming)

### Full Stack Web Developer at Little code, Split, Croatia

May 2020 — October 2021

### Tech stack:

- .NET C# development (.NET Core 3.1, .NET 5+)
- Frontend development (Angular2+, RxJs, REST, JSON API, TypeScript)
- HTML 5, CSS (SCSS) Bootstrap, Angular Material UI
- Cloud programming (Azure App Services, Azure SQL...)
- · Distributed programming
- Azure DevOps (Scrum, Azure Pipelines)
- . Git

During my time at Little code I worked as a developer for multiple Scrum teams, both remote and in-house.

My responsibilities varied from project to project.

Some examples: setting up projects from scratch, maintaining legacy codebases, PR reviewing, transcribing client demands into "developer" task...

### Web Developer at Gamma Chef, Split, Croatia

September 2019 — April 2020

#### Tech stack:

- .NET C# Framework 4.7 (MVC razor pages)
- Frontend development ( jQuery, CSS )
- Git

#### **Details**

Split, Croatia, +385 95 875 02 89 mislav.karanusic@outlook.com

#### Links

GitHub LinkedIn

#### **Skills**

C# .NET

Angular 2+

Microsoft Azure

SQL Server

### Languages

English

Croatian

I was brought in, in the final stages of the product to help remove bugs and polish the app for production environment.

# Most Notable Projects

## NaOku, (Business manager)

### **Technologies**

• .NET Core 3.1, C# Angular 10, Azure

### **Project details**

This project has 4 core components:

- Web app (Angular)
- Backend (.NET microservices)
- · Identity Server with Web interface
- Service health check

### App premise

It allows Erste Card Club clients (mostly large retail chains) to manage and view their traffic, payments, employees and contracts.

#### **App Screens**

# MoneyFlow v1, (Finance manager)

### **Technologies**

• .NET 5, C# Angular 11, Azure

### **Project details**

This project has 3 core components:

- User Mobile Client (Xamarin)
- Admin Web Client (Angular)
- Backend (.NET API)

### High level technical solution overview:

#### Backend API:

- · Rest API with swagger documentation
- · Azure Blob Storage configuration for storing receipt images
- Authentication/Authorization using Azure AD integration
- · Application Insights telemetry for analyzing the performance and usage
- Managing Azure AD user data through the Microsoft graph API
- UnitOfWork + Repository pattern
- Entity Framework Core code first
- · Push Notifications using Firebase Cloud Messaging
- Usage of Hosted Service for periodic code execution
- Flow for implementing exchange rates (multi-currency app)
- · Exporting data as CSV/PDF
- · Unit test coverage

### Admin Web Client (Angular):

· NgXs for global state managing

- Statistics charts
- · Firebase push notifications
- MSAL Angular authentication with Azure AD
- RxJS
- Design Angular Material + SCSS

CI - for this project is done with Azure pipelines with automatic deploys to the test environments after successful build event from development branches.

# Certification

**Microsoft Certified: Azure Fundamentals** 

July 2021

Verification

# Education

Computer engineering, Electro-technical School, Split, Croatia

2014 - 2018